families of veterans banding together is explosive new allegations surface from another whistleblower in the widening healthcare scandalous of VA
退伍军人联合起来的家庭是爆炸性的新指控从另一个举报人在扩大医疗丑闻弗吉尼亚州的表面
show of force a triumphant victory lap and Crimea Ukraine in some places citizen staring down time delay motherhood more than ever women waiting longer to have children the new report out tonight with some surprising number
炫耀武力凯旋胜利的把握和乌克兰克里米亚在一些地方公民盯着时间延迟母性比以往任何时候女人等待更长的时间才能有孩子提供一些数量惊人的新的报告今晚
the kill switch kit fits properly simple and effective in combating why isn't it available everywhere Nightly News
杀开关套件配合适当的简单而有效的打击为什么不是随处可见晚间新闻
headquarters in New York this is NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
总部设在纽约，这是NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
Healthcare scandal surrounding the Department of Veterans Affairs has now wife in the investigation that started with one VA hospital in Phoenix has intensified of spreading out from there including East Washington
退伍军人事务部医疗周围有丑闻现在的妻子与一个VA医院在凤凰展开调查力度不断加大从那里蔓延出来，包括东华盛顿
veterans families are now mobilize because of the charges that are returning vets have been ignored mistreated and have died because of this and a new whistleblower has emerged tonight telling NBCNews of an alleged effort to cook the books add another VA facility
退伍军人家庭现在调动，因为将要返回的兽医都被忽略虐待，因为这与已经死了，一个新的举报人今晚已经出现，告诉被指控的努力假账再添VA基金的NBCNews的收费
we begin tonight in Phoenix on today's visit there from a decorated veteran of happens to be in Arizona Senator John McCain NBC is Kelly O'Donnell in Phoenix covering for us tonight
我们今晚在凤凰城的一个老兵装饰在开始今天的参观，恰好是在美国亚利桑那州联邦参议员约翰·麦凯恩NBC是凯利·奥唐奈在凤凰城覆盖今晚我们
good evening Brian whistleblower how come forward to speak with NBC News what some practices were inside VA medical centers concerning patients and here in Arizona a town hall meeting brought the anger to the surface
晚上好布赖恩告密者如何出面发言，NBC新闻什么的一些做法在里面VA医疗中心的病人有关，在这里在亚利桑那州的一个市政厅会议上所带来的愤怒到了表面
I know in Phoenix today the groin controversy over veterans care is personal
我知道在今天凤凰腹股沟争论退伍军人护理是个人
endorphin painful much for them to see him it took months Family and veterans pulled out their frustrations visual people were not numbers
内啡肽痛苦多让他们看到他花了几个月的家庭和退伍军人掏出他们的挫折视觉人不是数字
Andrew greif my dad is no longer here and I know there is something done wrong
安德鲁·格雷夫我爸爸已经不在这里了，我知道有些事做错了
the Phoenix VA Medical Center is under investigation over allegations that staffers kept secret patient appointment list to conceal long waiting time from the official records Jim lily is a Vietnam veteran undercarriage Phoenix
凤凰VA医学中心正在调查过指控，员工保密门诊预约清单，从官方记录吉姆·百合是一个越战老兵底盘凤凰隐瞒漫长的等待时间
when you first learned about this winter
当你第一次了解了这个冬天
we were betrayed
我们被出卖了
Michelle Duggar veterans
米歇尔Duggar老兵
server country
服务器国
Senator John McCain's is the evidence he seemed so far to a cover up
参议员约翰·麦凯恩的是，他看起来是那么远，掩饰证据
when you met with the local VA officials to big knowledge and AlterNet patient list of course not
当你会见了当地官员弗吉尼亚州到大的知识，当然ALTERNET患者名单不
making sense full supply in patient wait times maybe widespread
决策意识充分供应耐心等待时间可能普遍
twin out here in reports of Atlanta Colorado to California number of other VA facilities with the same kind of scandalous procedures are being pursued
双出在这里科罗拉多州亚特兰大的报告，与同类丑闻程序等VA设施数量加州正在推行
Brian Turner is a VA Medical scheduling clerk in San Antonio Texas who says clerks work coach to change numbers and dates to a raceway time of weeks or months
布赖恩·特纳是在圣安东尼奥得克萨斯州VA医学调度办事员谁说文员的工作教练数字和日期更改至数周或数月的时间滚道
if you had a longer time from India 14 day window
如果你有从印度14天窗口较长时间
University Report
大学报告
tell you need to change this
告诉你需要改变这种
Turner says he has not seen a separate or secret waiting lists the claims she was told to change date
特纳说，他还没有看到一个独立的或秘密的等候名单，她被告知要更改日期的要求
my belief is that we are changing numbers in order for the VA to reflect
我的信念是，我们为了改变号码的弗吉尼亚州，以反映
if they have a shorter way.
如果它们具有更短的方式。
the San Antonio v8 old NBC News it review turners claims last month and found they were not substantiated
圣安东尼奥V8旧NBC新闻回顾它车工声称上个月，发现他们并不成立
McCain says he is disappointed in Veterans Affairs Secretary Eric Shinseki I would have expected
麦凯恩说，他感到失望的退伍军人事务部长埃里克·新关我本来期望
did him if this is as big as widespread as it appears to be a shoulda known
没有他，如果因为这似乎是一个众所周知早该这是大如广
Brian tonight new information from Wyoming NBC News has obtained an email written by Ashanti NBA Stafford to other employees that appears to offer coaching on changing the date it says quote
从怀俄明州NBC新闻今晚布莱恩新的信息已获得书面阿散蒂的NBA斯塔福德来，似乎提供其他员工的电子邮件执教于更改日期说帖
yes it is gaming the system a bit email goes on to say the front office get very upset when wait times are longer than 14 days without new information
是的，它是游戏系统有点电子邮件接着说前面的办公室很心烦时的等待时间是14天再没有新的信息
investigation office place employee on leave and said that if this is true the behavior is unacceptable
调查办公场所员工休假，并说，如果这是真的的行为是不可接受的
what a mess Kelly O'Donnell starting of our coverage from Phoenix tonight
什么乱七八糟的凯利·奥唐奈开始我们的覆盖范围从今晚凤凰城
retired US Army Colonel Jack Jacobs is here with us in the studio hyzaar military affairs analyst but more importantly
美国退役陆军上校杰克·雅各布斯在这里与我们在演播室海捷亚军事分析家，但更重要的是
he's the recipient of the Medal of Honor for his combat actions in Vietnam is also a recipient of VA health care is had to buy his reckoning somewhere north of 1000
他的荣誉勋章，他在越南作战行动的接受者，也是VA医疗保健收件人是当初买他精打细算的1000北部某处
Trey Songz coming home from the war still got some shrapnel in you I know you have looked around at the landscape and have a solution you've discovered that is right there in front
新人报到从战争回家还是得到了一些弹片在你，我知道你已经看了看周围的景观，并有你已经发现是正确的，在前面的一个解决方案
via is a huge bureaucracy that does with a seadoo best
通过是一个巨大的官僚与SEADOO最好呢
there's no way that we going to be able to get one
没有办法，我们将能够得到一个
federigo's the doctor doctor treats veteran and the government sets a doctor check to make it any more difficult for veterans meals that we broken trust with those with flat 4
federigo的医生医生对待退伍军人和政府制定医生检查，以任何更困难的退伍军人的饭菜，我们打破信任那些与平4
so your arguing for a total scrapping
所以你争论，总报废
what is not delivered what we need in a cantiliver what we need it census data cost a parallel system that doesn't give us what we need
什么是不传递我们需要在一个cantiliver我们需要它人口普查数据花费的并行系统，这并不能给我们带来什么，我们需要
Jack Jacobson comments he is submitting by the way to the New York Times will see what becomes of this idea Jackson
杰克·雅各布森评论他的方式向纽约时报提交将会看到怎样变成这个想法杰克逊
overseas tonight a triumphant defiance show of force by Vladimir Putin the day of the Russian president showed up in newly annexed Crimea
海外今晚胜利的蔑视秀武力普京俄罗斯总统当天在新近吞并克里米亚露面
does celebrate VE Day and about Putin's claim this week hold back his forces from the border with Ukraine
并庆祝胜利日以及有关普京的说法本周忍住他的部队从边境与乌克兰
US government today really satellite images saying they appear to show Putin's claim is not true the one on the left shows no Russian forces around about
今天美国政府真正的卫星图片说，他们似乎表明普京的说法是不正确的一个在左边显示周围没有俄罗斯军队约
stock Tober the one on the right showing them still there as of 2 days ago Archie foreign correspondent Richard Engel in Ukraine for us again tonight Richard Petty
股票TOBER一个上展示他们还在那里2天前阿奇外国记者理查德·恩格尔在乌克兰再次为我们今晚理查德·佩蒂的权利
good evening Brian it was another bold move from today is it in Crimea which until very recently what part of Ukraine State Department called it provocative NATO said it was inappropriate but he still came
晚上好布赖恩它是从今天的另一个大胆的举动是在克里米亚的，直到最近有什么乌克兰国务院的组成部分称之为挑衅北约说，这是不恰当的，但他还是来了
why isn't easily deterred today I'm a surprise visit he sailed to find little Russian naval base in the new leonexxx territory of Crimea and said affectively Russia is doing what it wants
为什么不容易却步今天我突然造访，他航行到找小俄罗斯海军基地在克里米亚新leonexxx领土和情感上说，俄罗斯正在做它想做的事情
everybody should respect our lives including restoring historic injustice
每个人都应该尊重我们的生活，包括恢复历史的不公
Putin believe the breakup of the Soviet Union was in injustice names to restore its glory
普京认为苏联的解体是不公正的名字来恢复它的荣耀
internet together under a statue of liberty to remember the victory over nothing
下自由地记得战胜任何的雕像一起上网
pro Russian militia men March 10
亲俄罗斯的民兵3月10日
they got big cheers for fighting another regime they called fascist
他们得到了很大的欢呼战斗另一个政权，他们被称为法西斯
here today to commemorate a little more but also for rally against the government in Kiev and they say it back
今天在这里纪念多一点，但也为集会反对政府在基辅和他们说这回
Mayport down the flowers gone on open truck pulls to the nearby city of Mario Paltz to join a bottle expand rating for 3 days
梅波特下来了开放式卡车花拉至附近的城市马里奥·帕尔茨中加入一瓶扩大评级3天
ukrainian troops had come in fours take the police station
乌克兰军队已经进来四肢着地采取了派出所
Russian militia
俄罗斯民兵
bullet
子弹
battle of the management nearby and then another and then pull it right over head ever
管理层的战役附近，然后再然后将其右头比以往任何时候都
trying on arm stop the truth eventually
试图在手臂阻止真相终于
Ukrainian soldiers manage to take the police station but now
乌克兰士兵设法采取派出所，但现在
it was burning the troops left
它在燃烧的部队离开
Astros a Pengui civilians overhead to hold the crowd back
太空人一Pengui平民开销持有人群后面
got into armored vehicles
钻进装甲车
Ukrainian government wanted to send a message to Folsom Alicia and their supporters today and it was willing to scorch the earth to do it
乌克兰政府今天要发送消息给福尔瑟姆艾丽西亚和他们的支持者，并愿意烧焦的大地做
officials hearsay 7 people were killed in Mario Paul today Brian could repeat itself in the coming days
官员道听途说7人在马里奥·保罗今天杀了布莱恩可能在未来几天内重演
Richard Engel again tonight from Donetsk Ukraine Richard thanks
理查德·恩格尔今晚再次从乌克兰顿涅茨克感谢理查德
we are learning in this country tonight about what could be a first in aviation Amir collision between a commercial airliner an unmanned drone app in the skies over Tallahassee Florida it happened back in March the pilot of the USA
我们今晚在学习这个国家的什么可能是第一个在航空阿米尔碰撞一架商用飞机在上空佛罗里达州塔拉哈西的无人驾驶飞机的应用程序它发生在三月的美国飞行员之间
what is regional jet apparently got so close to his aircraft he was sure he had collided with an inspection of the aircraft found no damage the FAA says it is investigating the incident
什么是支线飞机显然有这么接近他的飞机，他确信他已经相撞飞机的检查没有发现损害美国联邦航空局表示，正在调查这一事件
the NBA has turned to a veteran of the business world to become the interim CEO of the LA Clippers is richard Parsons a former chairman of Citigroup former head of Time Warner remove comes 10 days after the NBA banned owner Donald sterling from the Game of a racist comments he made
在NBA已经转向了商业世界的老将，成为洛杉矶快船的临时首席执行官理查德·帕森斯时代华纳的花旗集团前负责人的前任主席来删除10天后NBA的禁止老板唐纳德英镑从一个种族主义的游戏评论他做了
the league is trying to force a sale of the team in the meantime the Clippers play the Oklahoma City Thunder game 3 tonight at the Staples Center in LA series type 1 to 1
该联盟试图迫使一个销售团队的同时，快船在斯台普斯中心的LA系列1型打俄克拉荷马城雷霆比赛今晚3比1
as the man once said looks like we're in for nasty weather this spring weather patterns are going to make for a rough Mother's Day weekend for millions of people more weather dangerous head from the Great Lakes on down to the Gulf of Mexico some big cities in the severe threat area tonight including St Louis Memphis Houston
作为曾经说，该男子看起来我们是在为讨厌的天气今年春天天气模式要进行一个粗略的母亲节周末，数以百万计的人们更多的抵御危险的头从大湖，下至墨西哥湾的一些大城市在严重威胁区域今夜包括圣路易斯灰熊休斯敦
tomorrow the worst of it moves to threaten Kansas City Oklahoma City in on Sunday Mother's Day expands from Central Texas all the way north to Chicago and Beyond
明天最糟糕的移动威胁到堪萨斯城俄克拉何马城在周日母亲节扩大从德州中部一路向北到芝加哥和超越
and on this Mother's Day weekend new numbers out today show that more than ever before women are waiting longer to have children if they can afford to win the last decade or so it's been a 35 percent increase among women 40 to 44 having children for the first time
并在此母亲节周末新号码开出今天显示，超过以往任何时候女人之前等待更长的时间才能生孩子，如果他们能够赢得最后十年左右它已经40到44生儿育女的首位女性增加了35％时间
when theres this number over the past four decades on 900 increase among women over 35 having her first child we get more tonight from NBC's Janet shamlian
当theres这个数目在过去四十年的900间增加以上妇女有她的第一个孩子35我们从NBC的珍妮特shamlian获得更多的今晚
we want to make sure she's taking oral medications at 36 on Ellen Solomon has spend years building a prestigious career is it OB GYN surgeon but having a family with also part of a plant
我们要确保她服用口服药物在36埃伦所罗门已经花费数年时间建设一个有名望的职业生涯是产科妇科外科医生，但有一个家庭，也有部分植物的
need to do something before I became
需要做一些事情之前，我就成了
person looking to find anybody to marry just so I can have a baby
人希望找到人结婚，这样我可以有一个宝宝
22 years ago its 34l in frozen eggs at the Cleveland Clinic from mom Karen help pay for the procedure to growing number of women freezing eggs a younger age no longer considered experimental many states insurance against an uncertain future
22年前它在冷冻卵子在克利夫兰诊所的妈妈卡伦帮助支付程序，越来越多的女性冷冻卵子34升低龄不再被视为实验许多国家对不确定的未来保险
they don't have that Panic out of gotta get out and meet Mr Right they can accept that and hold and think about their career for a while and when the time is right they have their eggs to go back in in consider for transfer that point
他们没有这样的恐慌得出来的走出去，满足白马王子，他们可以接受，并保持和思考自己的职业生涯了一段时间，当时间是正确的，他们有他们的鸡蛋回去在考虑转让该点
freezing eggs expensive and really covered by health plan
冷冻卵子昂贵的，真正受健康计划
the average cost for one round 13001 annual storage fee amilonger woman wait the less likely eggs will be healthy
平均成本为一圆13001年储存费amilonger女人等待的可能性就越小蛋就会健康
gestational diabetes I was on insulin I'm having blood pressure issues
妊娠糖尿病我是在胰岛素我有血压问题
what did Max and Lily are doing great mothers day is a reminder of how lucky they are genital en NBC News Houston
什么也Max和莉莉正在做伟大的母亲节是他们是多么幸运生殖器恩NBC新闻休斯敦提醒
still having this Friday evening the kill switch
仍然有这个星期五晚上杀死开关
does just when it says a big part of a fight back against this nation
不只是当它说的斗争的重要组成部分背靠这个国家
phone taps in later is Apple about to make their largest purchase ever
手机水龙头后面是苹果即将作出自己的最大购买过
in California tonight there is new legislation that could start a trend that same to combating what's become a staggering number of smartphone thefts 1 in 10 Americans ARPANET
在加州今晚有新的立法，可以开始一个趋势，同样的打击是什么已经成为智能手机盗窃案1中10个美国人ARPANET的一个惊人的数字
if this new song called Killswitch effort is successful if consumed protect cell phone users across this country and a lot of people would love to know why they don't have it already forgot to report a knife from NBC's Miguel Almaguer in Los Angeles
如果这首名为KILLSWITCH的努力是成功的，如果在这个国家，有很多人消费保护手机用户很想知道为什么他们没有它已经忘了从NBC的米格尔Almaguer在洛杉矶报告一把刀
brazen cell phone robberies are the epidemic often carried out in daylight
厚颜无耻​​的手机劫案经常开展日光疫情
3.1 million Americans have their smartphone Stalin last year alone 110 Ave
310万美国人有他们的智能手机，斯大林，仅去年一年110大道
23 year old Megan boken with talking your mom on her new iPhone when it was stolen and she was shot to death
23岁的梅根·博肯与她的新的iPhone谈论你的妈妈，当它被偷走了，她被枪杀
quickly to stop
赶紧停止
Botkins family wants all cell phones to have a so-called Killswitch which they believe could have saved Megan's life
Botkins家人希望所有的手机有一个所谓的KILLSWITCH他们认为可能有救梅根的生活
create something with the phone becomes a brick literally a brick and does not work anymore it does if I burn peeling to steal it
创造一些与手机变成砖头从字面上一砖一不工作了它，如果我烧脱皮偷
California this and it just got a new smartphone which by next year software allows consumers to disable a device remotely rendering it useless
加州这一点，它只是得到了一个新的智能手机，其中明年软件使消费者能够禁用设备远程渲染它没用
the only way that we're going to put your just stop this is when we get to the point war 2 this device have a kill switch
我们打​​算把你刚刚停止这个唯一的办法是，当我们进入正题战争2这个装置有一个杀死开关
Critics the trade group that represents mobile carriers who make billions on cell phone insurance says safe to use their top priority the kill switch law
批评者表示移动运营商谁的手机保险使数十亿的行业组织说，安全地使用他们的最优先考虑的杀法切换
state by state technology mandates stifle innovation to the ultimate detriment to the consumer
国家通过国家技术授权扼杀创新，最终损害消费者
cell phones after the crime of opportunity what happens most often during the middle of the day Austin in a restaurant a study shows 3 out of 4 people would put themselves in danger
手机机会的犯罪是什么日子奥斯汀的一家餐厅的一项研究显示四分之三的人中间过程中最经常发生的事之后，会把自己处于危险之中
just to get their sell back
只是为了让他们回来卖
has a call if my stuff on at my pictures in my text messages
有一个电话，如果我的东西就在我在我的短信图片
Sarah McGuire was desperate when her cell phone was stolen she did what police say you should never do
莎拉·麦圭尔是绝望时，她的手机被偷了，她做了什么，警察说，你不应该做的
chased after this
在此之后追
what have people have been punched
有什么人被冲
how dangerous trend on the rise and now I proposed law a killswitch many believed could save lives Miguel Almaguer NBC News Los Angeles
多么危险的趋势在上升，现在我提出法律KILLSWITCH许多人认为可以挽救生命米格尔Almaguer NBC新闻洛杉矶
what how about Dr Dre perhaps you own a pair of Beats By Dre you certainly have seen them on the street on musicians on athletes looks like dry along with his partner fellow veteran music producer Jimmy iving meth hit the jackpot if the rumor talks with Apple are finalized
什么怎么样德瑞博士也许你拥有一对节拍德瑞你肯定已经看到他们在街上就对运动员的音乐家看起来像干与他的搭档同胞老牌音乐制作人吉米·艾尔文甲基撞大运，如果与苹果的传闻谈判的敲定
Applewood pay over 3 billion dollars for Beach Boys hits Hardware in streaming music service it would be Apple's biggest purchase ever in a big payday for drag capping a career in music
阿帕尔伍德工资超过3十亿美元的海滩男孩打在硬件流媒体音乐服务，这将是苹果有史以来最大规模的在一个大的发薪日为拖在音乐加盖了职业生涯购买
can a life that got off to a rough start in the Compton section of LA sometimes it helps to speak the local language its so true in so many foreign countries as it is in Boston
可以在生活中有了一个概略的开始在洛杉​​矶的康普顿节，有时它有助于讲当地语言的如此真实在这么多外国，因为它是在波士顿
where the highway sign is guys felt compelled to use the local dialect begging drivers use your blinker
那里的公路标志是人感到不得不使用当地方言乞讨的驱动程序使用您的信号灯
let's just say was some great affection there are some drivers in the Bay State who will be surprised to learn there's a device on the steering column in a car that can be used to signal your intention to change lanes
我们只能说是一些伟大的感情有在海湾国家的一些司机谁将会惊讶地得知有关于汽车的转向柱装置，可用于对信号的意图改变车道
when we come back tonight a lot of kids of all ages working overtime this weekend projects with dear mom
我们回来的时候，今晚有很多各年龄段的孩子们加班加点本周末项目，亲爱的妈妈
find me tonight did you know mothers day turns 100 years old this weekend it was President Woodrow Wilson who signed the proclamation declared in the second Sunday in May is mothers day
找我今晚你知道母亲节变成100岁这个周末是伍德罗·威尔逊总统是谁签署的第二个星期日五月宣布的宣布是母亲节
contrary to popular method was not signed by anyone named hallmark speaking of which however Cowboys cards are right now being bought or better yet made by children everywhere NBC's Romelu tonight inside the creative process with the help of some kids
与流行的方法并没有被任何人命名的标志说到这不过牛仔卡现在被收购或更好，但由孩子到处做NBC的Romelu今晚的创作过程与一些孩子们的帮助内签署
my name every Elijah my name is
我的名，无不以利亚我的名字是
this is Alex H
这是亚历克斯ħ
classmates in head
在头部的同学
do we see your car they got chords to make as special as their mom
我们看到了你的车，他们得到了和弦进行特殊的他们的妈妈
is marrying
被结婚
the also have plans to rain really make
的也有计划要下雨真正使
annealing
退火
Obama in mom
奥巴马在妈妈
show me how the Carnegie turned into something silly imagines with pictures
告诉我该怎么卡内基变成了一些愚蠢的不可想象用图片
smothered by children
儿童窒息
every car beautiful unique and full of gratitude Maine
每一辆美丽独特的，充满了感激缅因州
you always giving me black
你总是给了我黑色的
coral letting me watch movies
珊瑚让我看电影
cuddling 40
40拥抱
Mickey my lines
米奇我行
I love you
我爱你
NBC News New York
NBC新闻纽约
and that's what it's supposed to be about that's our broadcast on this Friday night in for this week thank you for being here with us on Brian Williams we hope to see right back here on Monday nights wishing all the moms out there a happy mothers day we wish you all a good weekend goodnight
而这正是它应该是关于这就是我们的广播在这个星期五晚上在本周感谢您能在这里和我们的布赖恩·威廉斯，我们希望看到的右后卫位置上周一晚上希望所有的妈妈们一个快乐的母亲节在那里我们祝大家周末愉快晚安